听力材料，第一节。
下面你将听到五段短对话，
每段对话后有一个小题。
从每小题所给的
,B What does the boy want to be when he grows up?
三个。
选项中，选出一个最佳答案。
听完每段对话后，你都有十秒钟的时间来回答有关小题和阅读下一小题。
每段对话只读一遍。
May I have your order, sir?
I'd like some noodles.
What size would you like?
A large bowl of beef noodles, please.
What kind of noodles does the man want?
What's your favorite subject?
My favorite subject is Chinese.
Why do you like Chinese?
Because I want to work in China after I graduate.
Question Where does the boy want to work after he graduates?
Who is that woman, Frank?
Oh, she is my music teacher, Miss Wu.
Do you all like her class?
Yes, she often teaches us new songs.
Question What does Miss Wu teach?
When is your birthday, Lin It's on October 1st.
Oh, it's on National Day.
Yes, I have the same birthday as our country.
Question When is Lin Tao's birthday?
第二节。
下面你将听到六段对话或独白。
每段对话或独白后有几个小题。
从每小题所给的
三个选项中，选出一个与你所听到的对话或独。
白内容相符的问题的答案。
听每段对话或独白前，你都有十秒钟的时间阅读有关小题。
听完后，每小题将给出五秒钟的作答时间。
每段对话或独白读两遍。
听第一段材料，回答第六至八小题。
What can I do for you, young man?
I want to buy a mobile phone.
What will you use it for?
For having classes at home.
I think this one will fit you.
It runs fast.
Do you have any other colors?
How about the white one?
It looks nice.
How much is it?
It's 2000 yuan.
Oh, I'll take it.
What can I do for you, young man?
I want to buy a mobile phone.
What will you use it for?
For having classes at home.
I think this one will fit you.
It runs fast.
Do you have any other colors?
How about the white one?
It looks nice.
How much is it?
It's 2000 yuan.
Oh, I'll take it.
Six What will the man use the mobile phone for?
Seven What color does the man like?
Eight How much will the man pay?
听第二段材料，回答第九至十一小题。
What's wrong with your throat, dear?
I feel a little sore,
Do you cough?
Once in a while.
I think you should drink some hot water first.
I just want to lie down and have a rest.
I'm afraid you should go to the hospital at once.
Okay. Shall I take the bus?
No. Let me drive you there.
Thank you. What's wrong with your throat, dear?
I feel a little sore,
Do you cough?
Once in a while.
I think you should drink some hot water first.
I just want to lie down and have a rest.
I'm afraid you should go to the hospital at once.
Okay. Shall I take the bus?
No. Let me drive you there.
Thank you. Nine What's wrong with the girl?
Ten What does the girl's dad ask her to do first?
Eleven How will the girl go to the hospital?
How will the girl go to the hospital?
听第三段材料，回答第十二至十四小题。
How was your summer vacation, Lily?
Pretty good. I had great fun.
Where did you go for the vacation?
Shanghai, the biggest and most beautiful city in China.
How was the weather there?
It was hot.
Sometimes I had to go out in the evening.
Who did you hang out with?
My cousin. She has taught there in a university for two years.
Oh, she must be a good guide.
That's true. We visited many parts of the city.
How was your summer vacation, Lily?
Pretty good. I had great fun.
Where did you go for the vacation?
Shanghai, the biggest and most beautiful city in China.
How was the weather there?
It was hot.
Sometimes I had to go out in the evening.
Who did you hang out with?
My cousin. She has taught there in a university for two years.
Oh, she must be a good guide.
That's true. We visited many parts of the city.
Questions 12. Where did go for her vacation?
13. How was the weather there?
How was the weather there?
14. did Lily hang out with?
Who did Lily hang out with?
听第四段材料，回答第十五至十七小题。
Do you often play volleyball,
Yes. I play it twice a week.
How long have you played it?
Since 2018. Why do you keep playing it so long?
I think it's a good way to relax for study.
Oh, I see.
What's your hobby, Tom?
I like drawing.
I can draw a beautiful picture in a few minutes.
That sounds amazing.
Do you often play volleyball, Lucy?
Yes. I play it twice a week.
How long have you played it?
Since 2018. Why do you keep playing it so long?
I think it's a good way to relax for study.
Oh, I see.
What's your hobby, Tom?
I like drawing.
I can draw a beautiful picture in a few minutes.
That sounds amazing.
Questions 15. How often does Lucy play volleyball?
How often does Lucy play volleyball?
16. does Lucy think of playing volleyball?
17. What's Tom's hobby?
What's Tom's Have you ever been to Xiangyang?
听第五段材料，回答第十八至二十小题。
Yes. It was five years ago, but it changes a lot.
Yes. This new high -speed railway station looks modern and beautiful.
Is it far from the center of the city?
Yes. But the bus is convenient.
Which bus should we take to the hotel?
Bus number G003.
Where shall we visit first after we get there?
Let me show you around the city first.
That's great. When will we visit Longzhong?
Tomorrow. It'll take us about a day there.
That's great. visit It'll
When did the man come to
When did the man come to Xiangyang?
Xiangyang? Xiangyang? Xiangyang?
Which bus are they going to take?
Where will they visit tomorrow?
听第六段材料，回答第二十一至二十五小题。
Have you heard the story of Chi Mei Yan and Chi Mei Ling?
They are sisters.
were born together, went to school together, together,
worked together. They planned to marry at the same time on March 1, 2020, but they
changed their minds.
They volunteered to join the medical team.
They came to Xiangyang by plane on February 14.
They In order to save more time to take care of the patients, they cut off their
beautiful long hair before leaving.
began to work as soon as they got to Xiangyang Central Hospital.
They looked after the patients carefully, day and night.
Although they were in the same hospital, they were too busy to meet each other.
They worked in Xiangyang for about 36 days.
On March 21, they finished their work and left Xiangyang with the medical team.
When they left, people of Xiangyang saw them off in tears on both sides of the road
to the airport.
Their story not only moved everyone in Xiangyang, but also moved Mei Yun.
He said that he was one of the sisters' family members, and they could call him
Uncle Ma. He told them not to forget to invite Uncle Ma when they marry.
Have you heard the story of Qi Mei Yan and Qi Mei Ling?
Have They are sisters.
They were born together, went to school together, and worked together.
They planned to marry at the same time on March 1, 2020.
But they changed their minds.
They volunteered to join the medical team to help Xiangyang.
They volunteered to Xiangyang by plane on February 14.
In order to save more time to take care of the patients, they cut off their
beautiful long hair before leaving.
They began to work as soon as they got to Xiangyang Central Hospital.
They looked after the patients carefully, day and night.
Although they were in the same hospital, they were too busy to meet each other.
They worked in Xiangyang for about 36 days.
On March 21, they finished their work and left Xiangyang with the medical team.
When they left, the people of Xiangyang saw them off in tears on both sides of the
road to the airport.
Their story not only moved everyone in Xiangyang, but also moved Ma Yun.
He said that he was one of the sisters' family members, and they could call him
Uncle Ma. He told them not to forget to invite Uncle Ma when they marry.
Questions. 21. When did the two sisters plan to marry at first?
did the two sisters plan to marry at first?
22. How did the two sisters come to Xiangyang?
How did the two sisters come to Xiangyang?
23. Why did the two sisters cut off their long hair?
did the two sisters cut off their long hair?
24. How long did the two sisters work in Xiangyang?
How long did the two sisters work in Xiangyang?
25. What did Ma Yun let the two sisters call him?
What did Ma Yun let the two sisters call him?
25.